<resources>
    <string name="app_name">En2Bo Transliterator</string>

    <string name="welcome_title">WELCOME TO\nENGLISH TO BODYIG|TIBETAN TRANSLITERATOR</string>

    <string name="how_to_title">PLEASE READ : \n How to Use This Keyboard</string>
    <string name="how_to_steps">
        After Installing :\n
        1. Open your phone\'s Settings.\n
        2. Go to General Management > Keyboard list and default.\n
        3. Turn on the switch for \"En2Bo Transliterator\".\n
        4. Open any app with a text field (like Messages).\n
        5. Tap the keyboard icon in the bottom-right corner.\n
        6. Select \"En2Bo Transliterator\" from the list.\n\n
        <b>Important:</b> This app is the container for the keyboard service. Please do not uninstall it, or the keyboard will be removed.
    </string>

    <string name="about_title">About This Project</string>
    <string name="about_description">
        An English to Tibetan Transliterator.
        This keyboard allows people to type Tibetan words more easily on mobile phones\n
        English letters that match the pronunciation of Tibetan words are automatically transliterated into
        Tibetan script.
    </string>

    <string name="story_title">My Motivation</string>
    <string name="story_description">
        As a Tibetan refugee, this project is deeply personal. I believe that a culture is built upon
            the foundation of its language. With our country lost and our culture facing systematic elimination,
            preserving our language is not just a choice but an act of survival.\n\n
        I\'ve watched, with a heavy heart as my own generation turns to English for texting and social media,
            not out of preference, but for convenience and I Understand it as this is my story too. \n
        I used to be confident with my Tibetan in school years, but these days I find myself struggling to
        compose a formal application or even a simple poem in Tibetan which used to be very easy\n\n
        The connection to our rich written heritage is fading, even for those of us who speak Tibetan every day.
        I realized a major barrier with motive of typing in Tibetan and use of it while chatting with friends for
        example wasn\'t a lack of desire, but a lack of modern tools. The standard Tibetan keyboard on mobile phone
        is complex and due to concept syllable stacking of Tibetan, is difficult and slow to use on a mobile phone.\n
        This keyboard is my small contribution to changing that. By making it fast and intuitive to type Tibetan
        phonetically, I hope to remove that technical frustration. \n
        My dream is to see our digital spaces filled with our beautiful script, strengthening our community and
        ensuring our language—the soul of our culture—thrives for generations to come. Encouraging more people,
        especially Tibetans the younger generation, to use Tibetan as their primary language in purpose such
        as texting on social medias or any use case they find.
    </string>
</resources>
